<strings>
    <!-- <string id="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string id="nav_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string id="nav_products">Products</string>
    <string id="dropdown_thermal">Thermal Management</string>
    <string id="dropdown_jaundice">Jaundice Management</string>
    <string id="dropdown_ventilation">Non-Invasive Ventilation System</string>
    <string id="nav_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string id="nav_home_blue">Home</string>
    <string id="nav_about_us_blue">About Us</string>
    <string id="nav_products_blue">Products</string>
    <string id="dropdown_thermal_blue">Thermal Management</string>
    <string id="dropdown_jaundice_blue">Jaundice Management</string>
    <string id="dropdown_ventilation_blue">Non-Invasive Ventilation System</string>
    <string id="nav_contact_us_blue">Contact Us</string>
    <string id="footer_description">IQ Medical Systems is an ISO 13485 certified organization. We value the highest production standards, uncompromising quality of materials and component parts with attractive design. We are a globally oriented enterprise aiming at satisfaction of the customer's need all over the world.</string>
    <string id="footer_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string id="footer_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string id="footer_products">Products</string>
    <string id="footer_thermal_management">Thermal Management</string>
    <string id="footer_ventilation_system">Non-Invasive Ventilation System</string>
    <string id="footer_jaundice_management">Jaundice Management</string>
    <string id="footer_iso_certification">An ISO Certified Company</string>
    <string id="footer_copyright">Copyright © 2025 IQ Medical Systems. All Rights Reserved.</string>
    <string id="footer_designed_by">Designed by Roopsai</string> -->
    <!-- <string id="nav_aboutus_home">Home</string>
    <string id="nav_aboutus_aboutus">About Us</string> -->
    <string id="company_name">IQ MEDICAL SYSTEMS</string>
    <!-- <string id="about_us_title">ABOUT US</string> -->
    <string id="about_us_text_1">IQ Medical Systems has been developed as a low-cost alternative in the field of neonatology by designing and manufacturing products for newborns. This requires high-quality care for Resuscitation, Thermal Care, Hyperbilirubinemia Management, and other Pediatric Products. We are an ISO 13485 certified organization. Since the founding year of 2012, our company has exported products to many countries across the globe.</string>
    <string id="about_us_text_2">We value the highest production standards, uncompromising quality of materials, and component parts with attractive design. We are a globally oriented enterprise aiming at the satisfaction of customers' needs all over the world. The product line of IQ Medical Systems is the result of decades of experience in neonatal care equipment. Our focus is on patients' needs along with a user-friendly system for caregivers.</string>
    <string id="mission_title">Our Mission</string>
    <string id="mission_text">At IQ, our mission is to provide accessible and equitable Maternal and Neonatal care through innovative solutions and fostering partnerships with healthcare providers.</string>
    <string id="vision_title">Our Vision</string>
    <string id="vision_text">At IQ, our vision is to be the global beacon of pioneering maternal and neonatal healthcare, driving innovations that redefine the standards of well-being for mothers and newborns.</string>
    <string id="professional_team_title">Our Professional Team</string>
    <string id="professional_team_text">Assists healthcare providers in analyzing and choosing the right products along with successful installation, training, and maintenance.</string>
    <string id="product_range_title">Our Product Range</string>
    <string id="product_range_text">Neonatal & Pediatric Intensive Care Equipment like Radiant Heat Warmers, Neonatal Resuscitation Units, Intensive Care Infant Incubators, High-Intensity LED Phototherapy Systems, Non-Invasive Ventilation System, Smart Interfaces & Consumables, Resuscitation Equipment, Resuscitation Accessories & Kits, etc.</string>
    <string id="founder_name_1">Mr. Ayyappa</string>
    <string id="founder_position_1">Founder</string>
    <string id="founder_text_1">Mr. Ayyappa, qualified as a Biomedical Engineer, started his career in 1984-85 by servicing biomedical equipment for a few years and identified a gap in the field of neonatology equipment in India. He grabbed this opportunity and founded IQ Medical Systems Pvt. Ltd in 2007. He has been dedicated to continuous design and development of neonatal care equipment, producing cost-effective and reliable Infant Care Systems.</string>
    <string id="founder_text_2">These are widely used in Government, Non-Government, Military Hospitals, Medical Colleges, Trust Hospitals, Private Clinics, etc., throughout India. Through continuous feedback and appreciation from renowned neonatologists, IQ has built its brand value in India with quality, consistency, and goodwill.</string>
    <string id="founder_name_2">Mrs. Bhargavi</string>
    <string id="founder_position_2">Managing Director</string>
    <string id="founder_text_3">Mrs. Bhargavi, a qualified Biomedical Engineer, started her career as a director at IQ in 2018. Her ground-level experience helped her in spearheading the introduction of new products and widening the range of IQ Medical product offerings.</string>
    <string id="founder_text_4">She has been instrumental in promoting the concept of Non-invasive ventilator products in India since 2020. Her achievements and focus on building customer relations globally drive IQ Medical to achieve its vision and mission of being a “One Stop One Solution” in neonatology.</string>
    <string id="manufacturing_header_1">A GLIMPSE OF OUR</string>
    <string id="manufacturing_header_2">MANUFACTURING UNIT</string>
    <string id="manufacturing_text">IQ Medical Systems has the most integrated operations encompassing a great Quality Assurance and R&D section. The facility boasts of personnel with expertise in manufacturing and testing of Medical equipment and custom engineered solutions as per customer requirement. The plant is committed towards healthcare initiatives and focused on the advancement of the neonatal care industry. To complement its global trust, the manufacturing facilities of IQ have been upgraded and modernized to international standards. These facilities have been inspected and approved by international regulatory authorities for the supply of IQ's products to the respective markets.</string>
</strings>
